

TEAR 3 ONDERGRADUATI

□ (+86) 13201851252 | ■ JinduWang@hotmail.com | ★ hippodu001.github.io

About_

I'm JinduWang, a Year 3 undergraduate in Software Engineering, Xi'an Jiaotong University. My research interests lie in Human-Computer Interaction (HCI). My research is focused on how to better understand users' intentions and improve users' experience in VR/AR/MR systems., which follows three connected threads: 1)Design and evaluate innovative input or output interaction methodologies and technologies. 2)Develop context-aware and adaptive user interfaces. 3)Understand and model user behavior

Education

Xi'an Jiaotong University Xi'an, China

B.Eng in Software Engineering 2020.9 - Present

Neuromatch Academy Online

DEEP LEARNING SUMMER SCHOOL 2021.7-2021.8

Experience

Institute of Software, Chinese Academy of Sciences

RESEARCH INTERN 2022.7 - Present

• Advisor: Prof. Teng Han

Lenovo Research

Beijing, China

RESEARCH INTERN 2022.7 - Present

• Advisor: Researcher Nianlong Li

Intelligent Interaction Lab, Xi'an Jiaotong University

RESEARCH ASSISTANT 2022 10 - Present

· Advisor: Prof. Zhongmin Cai

Beijing Digital Force Field Technology Co., Ltd

UNITY PROGRAMMER INTERN 2022.6

Y PROGRAMMER INTERN 2022.8

Research_

BendStick: Bendable Stick Controller for Enhancing Ray-Based Interactions with Virtual Objects

In progress for UIST2023

SUPERVISOR: RESEARCHER NIAN-LONG LI AND PROF. TENG HAN

2022.7 - Present

Beijing, China

Xi'an, China

Beijing, China

- Co design a bendable stick controller that provides extra input dimensions like double rays via physically bending, thus enables complex tasks like object manipulation, and its holding postures.
- Co design and develop user studies to compare the control accuracy of different holding postures and evaluate the efficiency of BendStick in spatial object manipulation.
- Develop demos to demonstrate the potential applications of BendStick.

Context-aware AR Interfaces for Workspace with Both Virtual and Physical Displays (First author)

In progress for UIST2023

SUPERVISOR: PROF. ZHONGMIN CAI

2022.11 - Present

- Investigate previous work on context-aware interfaces in VR/AR/MR
- Design and develop and evaluate the context-aware AR display system to dynamically provide complementary information whilst we are mainly using a physical display, which includes designing layouts of AR displays, inputs(extrinsic and intrinsic), outputs and methods of the system, and user studies to evaluate.

Body-Centric Mixed Reality Input Technology

In progress for CHI2024

2022.12 - Present

MENTOR: XIANG LI(PHD. STUDENT IN CAMBRIDGE UNIV.)

- · Co build the design Space and analyze user's sense of ownership for a novel body-centric MR input technology
- · Co develop and design user stules to evaluate the novel body-centered interaction technology.

Honors and Awards

| - | Xi'an Jiaotong University Scholarship, | 2022.11 |
|---|--|---------|
| - | Wang Shishao and Qiu Qizhen Scholarship, | 2022.7 |
| - | China Merchants Bank Scholarship, | 2022.3 |
| | China College Students' 'Internet+'Innovation and Entrepreneurship Competition, Gold Prize | 2022.10 |
| - | (Project:Augmented Reality Knowledge Forest) | |
| - | Software Patent Certification, Apple App Store: ARKF | 2022.4 |
| - | Bluebridge Cup National Software Development Competition, Third Prize (Java Group) | 2022.4 |
| - | Tencent Cloud Practitioner Certification, | 2021.11 |
| - | National College Student Psychology Committee Top 100 Member, | 2021.10 |
| | | |

Technical Skills _____

Programming

CSHARP, JAVA, PYTHON(PYTORCH), GLSL, C/C++, OPENGL

Software and Tools

UNITY3D(VR,AR), MYSQL, LATEX, USER STUDY DESIGN, VISIO